tsp.gov 2016-12-03

# TSP: Website Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting the Federal Retirement Thrift Investment Board's (FRTIB) website(s) and reviewing its privacy policy. The FRTIB is committed to protecting the privacy of Thrift Savings Plan (TSP) participants, their beneficiaries, and others who visit its websites.

FRTIB's policy for both its websites (www.tsp.gov and www.frtib.gov) is that no personal information about you is collected unless you provide it to us in order to access your account.

### Information Automatically Captured and Stored

#### Public Website Access

The public components of the FRTIB and TSP websites do not collect any personal information about you. When you browse, read pages, or download information on the FRTIB or TSP website, we automatically gather and store certain technical (non-personal) information about your visit. This information is only used to help make the sites more effective and user-friendly.

Information automatically collected and stored includes:

  * Information about your connection to our Web server, including the Internet domain and IP address from which you access our website;
  * Information about your computer, including details about your computer's operating system;
  * Information about the Web browser and supporting technologies you use to access our site;
  * The date and time you access our sites; and
  * Addresses of referring websites.

In addition, this website uses Google Analytics. Please refer to the following policies on Google's website for more information:

#### TSP Account Access

If you choose to access your account in the secure section of the TSP website (www.tsp.gov), we do request your account number (or user ID) and Web password in order to identify your account. When you provide your account information, you are consenting to the electronic transmission of the personal financial information you have requested. Your consent is effective during the entire time you are accessing your TSP account through the website.

We only share information you give us with other government agencies if your transaction relates to another agency, or as otherwise required by law. Read the warning on the login page.

The TSP does not use Google Analytics on the My Account section of the website. Your account data is not available to Google or any other third party.

### Comments Submitted Online

The www.tsp.gov website allows users to submit comments. Submission of these comments is voluntary; however, you are deemed to have consented to the use of any data you provide. We will use the information you provide only for the reasons you provided it.

### Cookies

Cookies are pieces of information sent from the Web server to your browser and stored for a period of time. You can configure your Web browser to accept or decline cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent from the Web server. You do not have to accept cookies, but if you choose not to, some of the functions on the TSP website may not be available to you. There are two types of cookies: "persistent" cookies and "temporary", or "session", cookies.

Persistent cookies are pieces of information sent by a Web server to your browser and stored on your computer. We use this type of cookie to track your usage of the My Account section of the TSP website across sessions. Since the My Account section of the website contains personal information, these cookies may also include personal information. We use persistent cookies only in My Account and not in the TSP public websites.

We also use temporary or session cookies. These cookies are stored in memory and are only available during an active browser session. We use this type of cookie to track user sessions in order to analyze site usage. We do not collect or store any personal information with this type of cookie. These cookies are erased as soon as you close your Web browser.

### Security Monitoring

To ensure that the TSP website is secure and that this website is available to all users, the Government computer system employs software programs to monitor network traffic in order to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or damage the functioning of the website.

Unauthorized attempts to add and/or change information on this website are strictly prohibited and are subject to prosecution under the Computer Fraud and Abuse Act of 1986 (18 U.S.C. § 1030).
